Guide to Joel Simpson's Research Documents and Notes on the United Nations, 1970-1980
Department of Special Collections
Simpson, Joel. Research Documents and Notes on the United Nations,,
1970-1980
M1116
Simpson, Joel
1 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Includes research notes and documents on the United Nations collected by Joel Simpson.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Transferred to Special Collections, 2000.
Acquisition Information
Transferred to Special Collections, 2000.
Biography
Little is known of Joel Simpson.
Scope and Content
Consists of subject and agency files relating to United Nations work from the early 1970s thru the 1980s.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
United Nations--Study and teaching.
Collection Contents
- Security Council May 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Economic Documents1981 (?) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Amnesty International South America Prison Report1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Agrarian Reform7/1979-7/1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Afghanistan1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Decolonization1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Diplomatic Relations1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- East Africa1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- East Timor1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Energy1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Falkland Islands1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- GenocideNo Date (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Human Rights1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Nambia1961-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Non-use of Force in International RelationsNo Date (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Palestinian Refugees1949-1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Space Flight1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Puerto Rico1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Puerto Rico1898-1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- US Policy Towards South Africa1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)